Carl Neuberg Papers ca.1880-1956 1940-1956 Mss.Ms.Coll.4
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1970-1975; 3 lin. feet
  Correspondence, with some notes and miscellaneous material, received by Carl Neuberg, primarily after his emigration to the United States. Among the main correspondents are E. Abderhalden (1945-1949), on differences between American and German science and on Max Bergmann; R. Adams (1946-1948), on Adams's impressions of postwar Germany; L. Anschütz (1948-1955); H.C.S. Aron (2 files, 1942-1955); Adolf Butenandt (1947-1956); H. J. Deuticke (1951-1956); Hans von Euler (1947-1956); Claude Fromageot (1940-1953); Hans Gaffron (1943-1956) on research interests and technical and social issues; Otto Hahn (1947-1956) on issues related to Neuberg's directorship of the Kaiser-Wilhelm Institute; Kurt Jacobson (5 folders, 1924-1956), scientific, professional, and personal communications; D. Mazia (1955-1956) on Neuberg's difficult times in America; Otto Meyerhoff (1947-1949); L. Michaelis (1947-1949); D. Nachmanson (1947-1945); Friedrich Franz Nord (1942-1956); Severo Ochoa (1947-1955) on important aspects of Ochoa's career; K. G. Stern (1943-1956) on interesting professional issues; Otto Warburg (1948-1956); and H. Wieland (1946-1955), on German and American chemistry and common colleagues.
  - Abbott Laboratories, 1943-44 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Abderhalden, Emil, 1945-49 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Abderhalden, R, 1948 (Box Series I: Series I: 1)
  - Academic Press, 1942-56; 2 folders (Box Series I: 1)
  - Adams, Roger, 1946-48 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Ackermann, D, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Addinal, C. R, 1946 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Adenauer, Konrad, 1954 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Advances in Carbohydrate Chemistry - Corresp., 1945-46 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Advances in Enzymology - Corresp., 1953-55 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Agricultural Research Station - Rehovot, 1941 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Agrikulturchemisches Institut, 1952-55 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Akademie der Wissenschaften - Gàttingen, 1947-51 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Akamatsu, S., 1951-56 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Albaum, Harry G., 1951 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Alberty, 1953 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Alexander, Jerome, 1941-42 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Alrose Chemical Co., 1948 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Almond Products Company, 1944 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1944-51 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Brewer, 1942-52 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Cancer Society, 1949-56; 5 folders (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Chemical Society, 1944-56 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Chemical Society - Journal, 1942-52 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Christian Palestine Committee, 1952 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Cyanamid & Chemical Corp., 1945-53 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Friends of the Hebrew University (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Institute of Biological Sciences -Handbook of Biological Data, 1952 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Jewish Literary Foundation, 1955 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American League for a Free Palestine, Inc., 1944 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Lecithin Company, 1942-44 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1950 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 1945-54 (Box Series I: 1)
  - American Society of European Chemists and Pharmacists., 1948-54 (Box Series I: 1)
    See: Carl Neuberg Society for International Relations
  - American Society of European Chemists and Pharmacists Membership certificate, 1951 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Ammon, R, 1953-56 (Box Series I: 1)
  - Analytica Chimica Acta, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Andreas, Thales, 1947 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Anheuser-Busch, Inc., 1942-56 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Annual Review of Biochemistry, 1944-55; 2 folders (Box Series I: 2)
  - Anschütz, Anni, 1949 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Anschütz, Ludwig, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Antoniani, Claudio, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Antonoff, George, 1942 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Araki, Choji, 1954 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Arams, Alice, 1942 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Arapahoe Chemicals, Inc., 1947-52 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1943 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Archives of Biochemistry, 1942-56; 3 folders (Box Series I: 2)
  - Armed Forces Medical Library, 1954 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Armour Laboratories, 1947 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Arndt, Franz, 1954 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Aron, Hans C.S., 1942-55; 2 folders (Box Series I: 2)
  - Ascoli, Alberto, 1947 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Ascorbic Acid, 1922-40 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Atlas Powder Co., 1944-49 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Aub, J. A., 1944 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Aubel, E, 1949 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Aufbau, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Augstein, Ilse, 1947 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Auhagen, Ernst, 1948-56 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Avoset Co., 1948 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Axelrod, Bernard, 1947 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bacher de Eis, Alfred A, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Baeck, Leo, 1953 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Baecker, Benno, 1943 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Baer, Erich, 1954 (Box Series I: 2)
  - J.T. Baker Chemical Co., 1942-46 (Box Series I: 2)
  - P. Ballantine & Sons, 1942 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bamann, E, 1954 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Barken, G, 1943-44 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Barnicoat, C R, 1955 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Baron, n.d. (Box Series I: 2)
  - Barrenscheen, H. K., 1952 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Baudisch, Oskar, 1950 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bauer, Julius, 1952 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Farbenfabriken Bayer, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bayerische Akademie der Wissenschaften, 1951-52 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bayerische Vereinsbank, 1953 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bayerisches Staatsministerium für Unterricht und Kultus, 1952 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bazzi, Umberto, 1949 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Becker, Elmer L., 1952 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Behrendt, Ernst, 1953 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Beitcher, Kurt, 1955 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Beitzke, H., 1951-53 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Beitzke, Irma, 1951-53 (Box Series I: 2)
  - Bell, J., 1947-52 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bell, Russell, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bender, C. E., 1943 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Benesch, Reinhold and Ruth, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Benson, Arthur J., 1946 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Benton, Paul Bermann, 1942-56 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berenblum, I., 1951 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berg, George G., 1955 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berger, C. A., 1951 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bergius, Friedrich, 1948 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bergmann, 1916 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bergmann, Ernst, 1942-55 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bergmann, Felix, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bergmann, Gustav von, 1951-52 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berl, E, 1943 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berlak, H. L., 1952 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berlak, Marianne, 1946 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berlak, Millie, 1941-55 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berliner, Alfred, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bermann, Viktor, 1941-55 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bernard, S, 1956 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bersworth Chemical Co., 1948 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bernhauer, K, 1951 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bersin, Th, 1948-55 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Berthold, Herman, 1950 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Best Yeast, Limited, 1944 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Big, E., 1948 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Biochimica et Biophysica Acta, 1952-55 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Birsten, Vera, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Blakiston, Company, Inc., 1954 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Blank, Fritz, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bloch-Frankenthal, Leah, 1945-56 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Block, R. J., 1954 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Boaz, Friedrich, 1953 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bodecker, Charles F., 1956 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Boehm, Ernest, 1951 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bolcato, Virgilio, 1953-56 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bonhoeffer, K. F., 1953 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bonner, James, 1956 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Boscott, R. J., 1952 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bourdillon, Jaques, 1954 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Boyd, Eugene S, 1951 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brach, Ernst A., 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brand, Ervin, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1943 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Braun, H, 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Braunstein, A., 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Breitner, Burghard, 1949 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brent, Bernhard J, 1946-51 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Breusch, F. L., 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Briggs, A. P., 194 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brockhaus, F. A., 1953-54 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brockmann, Hans, 1955 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brode, Wallace R., 1948 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 195? (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brooklyn Medical Press, Inc., 1955 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute - inventory of chemicals and equipment (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brown, A. S., 1948 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Brown, John J., 1942 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bucky, Gustav and Frida, 1948-54 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Budowski, Pierre, 1948 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Bueb, 1917 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Buading, Ernst, 1947-54 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Buffalo Electrochemical Co., Inc., 1948-5 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Burk, Dean, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Burnott,Lee, 1944 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Business cards, n.d. (Box Series I: 3)
  - Butenandt, Adolph, 1947-56; 2 folders (Box Series I: 3)
  - Butts, J., 1952 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Byk, Heinrich, 1916-17 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cagan, Ralph, 1942-47 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cahen de Gossels, Melanie, 1942 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cahill, William M., 1942-44 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cahn, Alice, 1955 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Calgon, Inc., 1942-49 (Box Series I: 3)
  - California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1944 (Box Series I: 3)
  - California Packing Corp., 1944 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Calvin, Melvin, 1948-54 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cannan, R. Keith, 1952 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cantoni, Giulio L., 1952 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Carbide & Carbon Chemicals Comp., 1942-53 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Carl Neuberg Society for International Scientific Relations, 1964 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Carlsbergfondets Biologiske Inst., 1936 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Carson, S F, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Casper, Leopold, 1949-54 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cassel, Hans M., 1944 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Castor, John G.B., 1952 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Cattell, Jaques, 1942 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Celanese Chemical Corp., 1947 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Chectroff (?), Toby, 1943 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Chanley, T., 1954 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Chargaff, Ervin, 1953-55 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Chatelet, A., 1949 (Box Series I: 3)
  - Chemical Abstracts, 1952 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Chemical and Engineering News, 1947-52 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Chemical industries, 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Chemical Publishing Co., Inc., 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Chemische Werke, 1937 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co., 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - CIBA, A.G., 1948 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Clark, G. L., 1953 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Clark, R. Lee, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cleary, John Thomas, 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Coghill, Robert D, 1943 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cohen, Joseph, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cohen, Philip P., 1948 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cohen, Ralph, n.d. (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cohen, Seymour S., 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cohn, Adolf, 1943 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cohn, Reinhold, 1952 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Collatz, Herbert, 1951-55 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Colovick, Sidney P., 1952-55 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Commercial Solvent Corp., 1944 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cook, A. H., 1955 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Coper, Kurt, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Corbiere, Henri, 1953 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cori, Carl F., 1942-51 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Corn Products Refining Company, 1943-53 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Corn Products Sales, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Correns, Carl W, 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cosla, O. Kauffmann, 1948 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Cronheim, Georg E., 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Crossley, M. L., 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Crowheim, Elarenz, 1949 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Crown Heights Hospital, 1943 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Crowther, Joan P., 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Crzellitzer, R., 1944 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Daniels, William F., 1952 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Danon, J. Robert, 1956 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Davidson, Don, 1949 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Davies, Gertrude D. Maengwyn, 1945-55 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Davies, Rita, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1953 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dazian Foundation for Medical Research, 1943-50; 2 folders (Box Series I: 4)
  - DeBogoy, Eugene, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dehnert, Johannes, 1953 (Box Series I: 4)
  - DeMilt, Clara, 1953 (Box Series I: 4)
  - DeMoss, Ralph D., 1951 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Denslow, L. Alton, 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Derby, Roger A, 1943 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Deuel, Harry J., 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Deulofeu, Venancio, 1948 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Deuticke, Hans Joachim, 1951-56 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Deutsche Physiologisch-Chemische Gesellschaft, 1953 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Deutsche Staatszeitung und Herold (New York), 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Deutsches Generalkonsulat - Amsterdam, 1939 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Diergarten, Harro H., 1955 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dirscherl, W., 1930-31 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dische, Zacharias, 1943-52 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Distillation Products, Inc., 1948-52 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dittmer, Karl, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Doering, William von Eggers, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Doerr, Carl, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dorer, Herbert, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Doudoroff, M., 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Dresel, Rita, 1948-51 (Box Series I: 4)
  - E.I. DuPont de Nemours Co., 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Durig, Adolf, 1953-54 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Durig, Arnold, 1946-54 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Durst, Robert F, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Duschinsky, R, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1942-48 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ebel, J. P., 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Edwal Laboratories, 1941-42 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1943-44 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ehrenberg, Paul, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ehrenstein, Maximilian, 1943 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ehrlich, Felix, 1942 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ehrman, Rolf, 1944 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Eirich, Frederick R, 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Eisenberg, Max, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Elias, Herbert, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Elias, Victor, 1955 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ella Sachs-Plotz Foundation, 1942-50; 2 folders (Box Series I: 4)
  - von Elmenau, Johannes, 1952 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Elsevier Publishing Company, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Elvehjem, Conrad A, 1943-44 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced (Box Series I: 4)
  - Foreign Medical Scientists, 1945 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Emerz, Arthur F, 1954 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Enders, Curt, 1948 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Endo Products, Inc., 1943-49 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Enzymologia, 1946 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Erlenmeyer, H., 1955-56 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Ernst-Reuter-Gesellschaft, 1954-55 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Euler, Hans von, 1947-56 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Excerpta Medica, 1947 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Experimental Medicine and Surgery, 1943 (Box Series I: 4)
  - European Steamship and Airways Agency, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 4)
  - Fairmount Chemical Co., Inc., 1942-43 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Farber, Eduard, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Farmer, Chester J, 1943-45 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feazel, C. E., 1952 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Federal Yeast Corporation, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feigenbaum, Jakob Ilany, 1941-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feigl, Fritz, 1946-54 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feigl, Hans, 1946 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feinberg, Abraham, 1952 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feitelberg, Serafima, 1944 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Feldmann, Leonhard, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Felix, Kurt, 1948 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fenchel, F. W., 1948 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fenwick, William, 1956 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frischel-Briess, Robert, 1943 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fischer, Franz Gottwald, 1947-56 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fischer, G., 1954 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fischer, H., 1954 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fischer, Hermann O.L., 1947-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fishberg, Ella, n.d. (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fishman, William H, 1951 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fleischhacker, Desider, 1945-48 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fleischmann Laboratories, 1942-56 121 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Flemming, Thomas P., 1955 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Flint, Eric, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fodor, Andor, 1942-54 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fodor, Paul J., 1947-54 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Foerst, Wilhelm, 1954 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fono, Andras, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Foote Mineral Co., 1943 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Forjaz, Pereira, 1952 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Forschungen und Fortschritte, 1955 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Forssman, Sven, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Forsyth, W. G. C., 1948 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Foss, Olav, 1953-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Foster, Jackson W., 1951 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fox Company, 1955 (Box Series I: 5)
  - France. Ministere des Affaires Etrangeres, 194o (Box Series I: 5)
  - Franck, James, 1955 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frank, 1951 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frank, Alfred, 1946-47 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frank, Fritz, 1948 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Franke, Eric E., 1956 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frankel, Max, 1947-51 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frankenburg, Walter G., 1943-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frankenthal, Lea, 1943-44 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frankfurter Bank, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frankl, Oscar, 1942 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fred, E. B., 1942-44 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Freie Universität Berlin, 1952 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Frenzen, E, 198 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Freund, R, 1941 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fried, Seraphine, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Friedberg, Felix, 1954-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1951 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Friends of the Universal Jewish Encyclopedia, 1944 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fritzsching, Erwin T., 1942-44 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Froehlich, A., 1953 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fromageot, Claude, 1940-53 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fruton, Joseph S., 1953 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Fulton, John F., 1953 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Funk, Casimir, 1954 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Furst, Walter M., 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gaffron, Hans, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gatt, Simon, 1951 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Geiger, Ernest, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Geiger, Rudolf, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gemant, Andrew, 1947 (Box Series I: 5)
  - General Beverage Corp., 1946 (Box Series I: 5)
  - General Biochemicals, Inc., 1952 (Box Series I: 5)
  - General Chemical Co., 1954-55 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Genevois, L., 1939-48 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gerriets, Jan, 1952 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gesellschaft Deutscher Chemiker, 1955 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gessler, A. E, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gey, K. Friedrich, 1953-54 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gibbs, Martin, 1954 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Ginsburg, Sara, 1946 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Ginzburg, Mary, 1942 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Gisel, Father Eugene A, 1948 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glaser, Hilde, 1943 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glass, Bentley, 1956 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glattfield, I., 1944 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glick, David, 1954 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glucuronolactone - Literature Briefs, n.d. (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glum, Friedrich, 1947-48 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glycerine - Misc., n.d. (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glycerine - Misc. correspondence, 1916 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glycerine manufacture - patents and reports, 1918-45 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Glycerine Producers' Association, 1944 (Box Series I: 5)
  - Goldenberg, Geromont & Co. - Chemische Fabrik, 1916-18 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Goldenberg, Harry, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Goldenberg-Oetker Stiftung, 1917-36 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Goldschmidt, Th., 1952 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Goldschmiedt, Henry, 1942-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gomori, George, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Goran, Morris, 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gottlieb, David, 1944 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gottschalk, A., 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gradenwitz, Felix, May 23, n.y. (Box Series I: 6)
  - Grauer, Amelie, 1948-51 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Great Western Sugar Comp., 1946 (Box Series I: 6)
  - R.W. Greef & Co., Inc., 1942-43 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Green, David E, 1943-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Greenstein, Jesse P., 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Greenwald, Isidor, 1942-55 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gregor, H. P., 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Grodman, Pearl Gladys, 1943 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gross, D, 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Grosse, Günther, 1952 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Grube, K. H., 1952 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gruenfelder, Benno, 1946-47 (Box Series I: 6)
  - de Gruyter, Walter & Co., 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gudemann, Josef, 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Guggenheim, M., 1947-55 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gusowski, Wolfgang S., 1946-47 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gustavson, K. H., 1952 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gutcho, M, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Guttman, Eugen, 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Gyorgyi, Albert Szent, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Haas, Erwin, 1952 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Haberland, U., 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hadra, Lisa, 1944 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hägglund, Erik, 1923-47 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Häusler, H., 1952-55 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Haffenreffer & Co., 1942 (Box Series I: 6)
  - HAGEDA (Handelgesellschaft Deutscher Apotheker), 1916 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hagstrom, W. C., 1953 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hahn, Amandus "Über die Dehydrierung der Bernsteinsäure", 1928 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hahn, Edith, 1953 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hahn, Hugo, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hahn, Otto, 1947-1956 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hakala, Reino W, 1951 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hall Laboratories, 1945 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hamburger, Adolf, 1941-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hamer, D., 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Handler, Philip, 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Happold, Frank C., 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Harovitz, Charles L., 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Harrow, Benjamin, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Harvey Society, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hassid, W. Zev, 1944-48 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hauptmann, Heinrich, 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Haurowitz, Felix, 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Haworth, Sir Norman, 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1940-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hedel, A. J., 1949 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heegaard, Erik, n.d. (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hehre, Edward J, 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1953-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heifetz, Harold, 1951 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heilbrunn, L. V., 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heineman, D. N., 1944 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heiss, J., 1953 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Helferrich, B., 1953-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Henderson, L. M. (Box Series I: 6)
  - Herbert, N. D., 1953 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Herbst, Robert M., 1943 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Herlinger, E., 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hermann, Siegvart, 1947-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Herrmann, George R, 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Herz, Hermann, 1942 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hestrin, S, 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heublum, R, 1945-46 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heubner, Lisa, 1946-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heubner, Wolfgang, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heuss, Th., 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - von Hevesy, G, 1951 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Heyden Chemical Company, 1944 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hirsch, Julius, 1947-53 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hochnuth, Ida, 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hockett, Robert C., 1943-51 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hofer, Gustav, 1951 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hoffmann, Julius C., 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hoffmann-Ostenhof, C., 1954 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hoffmann-La Roche, 1944-54 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hofmann, Eduard, 1948-55 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hofmann, Elsa, 1955 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Buchdruckerei Adolf Holzhausens, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hopkins, R. H., 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hoppert,Carl A, 1953 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Horovitz, J., 1947 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Huber, Wolfgang, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hudson, Claude, 1946-48 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, 1956 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hurie, W. L., 1948 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Huttrer, Charles P., 1943-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Hynes, W. A., 1948 (Box Series I: 6)